after breaking the rules of conduct
tras incumplir las normas de conducta
required in Big Brother Alex and Gustavo
exigidas en gran hermano Alex y Gustavo
have been disciplinarily expelled
han sido expulsados disciplinariamente
from the
del
contest in the gala this Thursday
concurso en la gala de este jueves se
the images that have
mostrarán las imágenes que nos han
forced us to make this decision will be shown luar this
obligado a tomar esta decisión luar esto
is a clip for telesalseo okay the first one in the
es clip para telesalseo vale el primero
morning the first one in the morning
de la mañana el primero de la mañana
how do you want to upload it now
como se lo quiere subir ahora
come on Oh they have hit each other
vamos Oh se han pegado
eh But where does it say that they have hit each other we
eh Pero dónde pone que se han pegado eso
have pulled that out of our
nos lo hemos sacado del
asses let's see a lot of people
culo a ver mucha gente
supporting it I don't I mean These are
apoyándolo yo no O sea Estos son
images I'm not going to do them a single
imágenes yo yo no les voy a hacer ni un
favor mao I don't want to know anything about them but the
favor máo no quio sa nada de ellos pero
worst thing about all
si es que a m lo peor de todo
this for me is that Big Brother This year I
esto yo es que gran hermano Este año no
'm not following it I'm not following it
estoy siguiendo no lo estoy siguiendo
because it hasn't caught my attention the
porque no me ha llamado la atención la
truth look that I loved Big
verdad mira que me encantaba el gran
Brother eh but the thing is that without Mercedes Mila it
hermano eh pero es que sin Mercedes Mila
stopped being the same that's why the
dejo de ser lo mismo es por eso la
consequence is this that they go laughing
consecuencia es esto que se van riéndose
from there to the room they go laughing they laugh at
de allí a la habitación van riendo se ri
the organization and they laugh at everyone they
la organización y se rien de todo Dios
laugh at us in our
que se van riendo de nosotros en nuestra
faces they laugh in our faces  from
cara que se rien en nuestra cara yo a
today on I don't want to know anything about
partir de hoy no quiero saber nada de
Yeah, I understand this was minutes
Ajá esto entiendo que ha sido minutos
ago okay They haven't accused them of
antes vale No han acusado ahora de
stealing bread now they
robarle el pan
accuse each other of keeping
se acusan unos a los otros de quedarse
food the problems that there are when
comida los problemas que hay cuando
hunger okay they are cheap scum for for for
hambre vale que son gentuza barata por
pride [ __ ] what is it that they are
por por orgullo [__] que es que nos van
laughing at us From there to their room
riéndose Desde allí hasta su habitación
and right now they are so calm
y están ahora mismo tan tranquilos
when Susana is destroyed it's not worth it
cuando está Susana destrozada no vale
because they had a problem
pues han tenido una movida
Look, of course, I mean this is what they do
Mira claro o sea esto es lo que hacen
when there is a problem okay he focuses, he
cuando hay una movida vale que enfoca
focuses on a flowerpot Or he focuses on whatever
que enfoca una maseta O te enfoca lo que
okay finally they remove censorship after the
vale por fin quitan censura tras la
expulsion of Alex and Gustavo Carmen to
expulsión de Alex y Gustavo Carmen a
Laura and Naomi this is the fault of habiles
Laura y Naomi esto es culpa de habiles
in the end whoever loses their temper loses let's
al final pierde quien pierde los
see no because Of course I understand that there have
ver no porque Claro entiendo que ha
been hours of censorship there have been hours
habido horas de censura ha habido horas
of
de
censorship while they were expelling them and it
censura mientras que los expulsaban y
happened La Movida is Spain it is the voice of
pasaba La Movida es España es la voz de
Spain wait Let's see what happens
España espérate Vamos a ver qué pasa
you know who has to win who wins the
sabes tenga que ganar que gane lo de
least important thing is that he wins is that you make a
menos es que gane es que tú hagas un
good contest enter let's have the people
buen concurso entr tengamos a la gente
Uy uy uy uy what
Uy uy uy uy que
nice moves that  It was
movidotas agradable que ha sido culpa
Deil's fault, let's tell you this hasn't
deil vamos te digo yo que esto no ha
been pleasant, it was Avilez's fault,
sido agradable ha sido culpa de
no, because you know, in the end, the one who
avilez no porque sabes al final pierde
loses their temper loses a little. And what does he
quien pierde los papeles un poco Y qué
do, he keeps
hace sigue
attacking me,
atacándome
wow. This is the
wow Este es el
panorama. Hey, but people are kind of
panorama Oye pero la gente está como
supporting one of the two, this guy.
apoyando mucho a uno de los dos al chico
Of course, I understand that there are no images. I understand that there are no images, of course.
este Claro entiendo que no hay
Hey, but everyone is
claro Oye pero todo el mundo está
supporting this guy,
apoyando A este chico
eh, I
eh
understand that there are no
entiendo que no hay
images. They must have met
imágenes se han encontrado en algún
somewhere in the house. They must have started
punto de la casa habrán empezado a
arguing. The most false saint, civila, and the one who
discutir la santa más falsa civila y la
set everything on fire with her evil and
que lo ha encendido todo por su maldad y
resentment. Jessica, who acts good and is the
rencor Jessica que va de buena y es lo
worst, acting underground and
más malo actuando subterráneamente y
making the spark jump. Now happy,
haciendo saltar La chispa ahora feliz
seeing herself as the winner. But she continues with her
viéndose ganadora Pero sigue con su
role and her voice. They must have
papel y su voz
met.
se han debido encontrar
Well, what a mess. They must have
Eh pues vaya movida se han debido
met somewhere in the house. And
encontrar en algún punto de la casa y y
that's what happened.
ha pasado eso